<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="changelog.xsl"?>

<changelog>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.8.1</version>
<time>2016-01-15T14:44Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed problems with AfxHookSource 0.2.8.0.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.8.0</version>
<time>2016-01-12T13:53Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_skip, allows to skip approximate demo ticks / demo time (front-end to demo_gototick command).
</change>
<change type="added">
Updated the mirv_streams system: It's far more accurate in many cases now, because it comes with
replacement shaders for SplineRope, SpriteCard, VertexLitGeneric (only non-bumped and non-phong shaders atm)
and UnlitGeneric (only non-bumped and non-phong shaders atm) and also uses UnlitGeneric as fallback material shader now.
Please note that the installation size increased heavily due to the shaders (196MB increase).
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
Please note: advancedfx.org recommends using alphaWorld and alphaMatteEntity (alphaMatte + alphaEntity) stream above matteWorld and matteEntity stream, since those are far superior!<br />
TODO: Add OpenEXR support for supporting the new depth24 action (24 bit depth streams export).
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.7.3</version>
<time>2015-12-26T18:13Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed render state problems once and for all hopefully (i.e. with D3DRS_SRGBWRITEENABLE state causing i.e. black console):
The render state or vertex / pixel shader constants overrides should now be properly transparent to the game (meaning the Get* actions
will feed the game with its own original values).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.7.2</version>
<time>2015-12-21T03:10Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_streams console warning / error spam about missing afx_* shaders that were not used anyway (unless you had set the hidden testAction to 1).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.7.1</version>
<time>2015-12-20T16:42Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed and re-added forcing of D3DRS_SRGBWRITEENABLE state for mirv_streams actions that require it (should fix i.e. wrong console colour).
</change>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_streams action stattrackAction for baseFx based streams (which most stream types except normal currently are).
Allows to fine tune the streams behaviour for the Stattrack weapon module and i.e. allows to make it invisible
( mirv_streams edit streamNameHere stattrackAction invisible ).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.7.0</version>
<time>2015-12-10T05:24Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated AfxHookSource: Adjusted to 9th Dec 2015 CS:GO update (affects mirv_deathmsg).
</change>
</changes>
</release>



<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.6.10</version>
<time>2015-11-11T16:45Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated AfxHookSource: Adjusted addresses according to 10th Nov 2015 CS:GO update. Also improved detection of m_skybox3d.scale to be more stable against CS:GO updates.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.6.9</version>
<time>2015-11-03T17:31Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated mirv_deathmsg highLightId: now works more POV demo alike: if the highlighted player dies the background is red.
</change>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_deathmsg highLightAssister: Whether or not to highlight kill assists for highLightId.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
Just so you know spddl released v1.0.0 of MMHud (the MovieMaker Hud to be used with HLAE).<br />
You can get it from here: http://mmhud.spddl.de/<br />
He is waiting for feedback, you should contact him here:
https://twitter.com/spddlde or http://www.spddl.de
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.6.8</version>
<time>2015-10-21T07:42Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_streams: Adjusted m_SkyBox3d.scale offset address according to 20th Oct 2015 CS:GO update, important for proper 3D skybox scaling in depth dump.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.6.7</version>
<time>2015-10-14T10:58Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added properties position, angles and fov to mirv_input, that can be used to set position / view angles / fov directly when in mirv_input camera mode.
</change>
<change type="updated">
Updated ScaleformUI override features. Will be documented in HLAE Manual as soon as appropiate - we are in contact with spddl.de regarding a special movie maker GUI :-)
(HLAE will automatically redirect requests from the game's folder csgo\resource\flash to a sub-folder path relative to HLAE.exe
called resources\AfxHookSource\assets\csgo\resource\afxFlash, but only if the file requested exists in the folder structure requested.)
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.6.6</version>
<time>2015-10-13T18:02Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added feature that overrides the ScaleformUI SWF file checksum checks, so you should be able to use custom HUDs / heavily customize your HUD. I am currently trying to contact someone that does custom HUDs in order to work out, if a special movie maker HUD can be made, but I am not in contact yet, let's see.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.6.5</version>
<time>2015-10-12T19:50Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_streams: Now forces motion blur off, in order to avoid problems with it  (The motion blur is not good anyway, you should add it in post production, if you want any.).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.6.4</version>
<time>2015-10-11T18:35Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added options to mirv_campath edit start: You can now give an absolute value or an delta value, enter mirv_campath edit into console for further help.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.6.3</version>
<time>2015-10-07T12:30Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_streams: Epileptic seizures are back, because off-screen rendering doesn't work well for streams that want the HUD to be drawn (drawHud 1), because the ScaleformUI doesn't obey the render target.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.6.2</version>
<time>2015-10-05T18:41Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added attachCommands and detachCommands properties to mirv_streams stream properties (allows executing commands when the stream is attached / detached), use at your own risk!
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.6.1</version>
<time>2015-10-04T19:17Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Add mirv_deathmsg highLightId - allows to disable frag highlighting or to set for which player id to highlight.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.6.0</version>
<time>2015-10-01T14:15Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Add mirv_snd_filter.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.5.1</version>
<time>2015-09-29T14:19Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated mirv_streams: alphaMatte and alphaEntity defaults (and thus alphaMatteEntity defaults) changed.
</change>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_streams edit not working properly in AfxHookSource 0.2.5.0.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.5.0</version>
<time>2015-09-29T06:32Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated mirv_streams record to give you less epileptic seizures (images are rendered off-screen now).
</change>
<change type="added">
Added alphaMatteEntity twin stream to mirv_streams, basically an entity stream with alpha channel (dumped in TGA format only).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.4.7</version>
<time>2015-09-25T12:55Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted AfxHookSource to 24th September 2015 CS:GO update (Affected depth stream skybox elements scaling, due to changes in CBasePlayer object.).
</change>
<change type="added">
Added several options for fine tuning mirv_input behaviour to mirv_input cfg.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.4.6</version>
<time>2015-09-20T20:09Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated mirv_streams: matteEntity stream clientEffectTexturesAction now defaults to noDraw in order to avoid problems with keying due to glow textures.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.4.5</version>
<time>2015-09-20T16:47Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed TGA file output header, which could cause problems i.e. in FFmpeg.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.4.4</version>
<time>2015-09-20T13:06Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_streams: Fixed D3DRS_SRGBWRITEENABLE FALSE state forcing, it's now on again on all stream actions that relay on it (depth, matte, black, white), since we can't relay on the engine at all to do it properly.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
Okay, hopefully this is the last fix of that type, at least for today :(
Sorry.
Happy testing, loool :D
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.4.3</version>
<time>2015-09-20T10:36Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_streams: Fixed D3DRS_SRGBWRITEENABLE state forcing (now forces the state both through IShaderShadow and manually, because the engine doesn't always update the state but still tracks it internally and updates it sometimes).
</change>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_streams: Adjusted m_SkyBox3d.scale offset address according to CS:GO update, important for proper 3D skybox scaling in depth dump.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.4.2</version>
<time>2015-09-20T09:02Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_streams: Fixed D3DRS_SRGBWRITEENABLE state forcing (now goes through IShaderShadow API and only for DebugDepth shader, so that shader state should get maintained by engine more properly), no more random colours and brightness hopefully.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
Oh boy was AfxHookSource 0.2.4.1 bugged, sorry for releasing it :/
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.4.1</version>
<time>2015-09-19T15:18Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated mirv_streams: Now handles error material (some fences on de_overpass have that currently).
</change>
<change type="updated">
Updated mirv_streams: Added alphaMatte, alphaEntity and alphaWorld streams (If you need alphaWorld depends on what you want to do.).
</change>
<change type="updated">
Updated mirv_streams: Most actions force D3DRS_SRGBWRITEENABLE state as required, to avoid random color states caused by the engine i.e. when decals are drawn in-between (until now only drawDepth action had this).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.4.0</version>
<time>2015-09-19T04:32Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated mirv_streams record: The recorded stream FOV will now match the game FOV.
</change>
<change type="updated">
Updated mirv_streams record name: is now a folder name, can be a full folder path (i.e. d:\myFoldeName). Default value is untitled_rec, which is a folder created where the csgo.exe is located.
</change>
<change type="updated">
Updated mirv_streams record: Take sub-folders will be automatically created in the folder specified by mirv_streams record name. The streams will go into sub-folders of the take folder accordingly.
</change>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_streams record format: Can be tga (default) or bmp.
</change>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_streams edit options for all streams: drawHud (default is 0), drawViewmodel (default is 1).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.3.5</version>
<time>2015-09-16T10:31Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_streams not handling auto bound materials in IMatRenderContext functions GetDynamicMesh and GetDynamicMeshEx.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
No HLAE problems with the latest 15th September 2015 CS:GO Update were found so far.
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.3.4</version>
<time>2015-09-13T19:49Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed a mistake in code that should not affect users.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.3.3</version>
<time>2015-09-13T18:18Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_streams screen flashing due to histogram adaption. For now HLAE will force mat_dynamic_tonemapping 0 when using mirv_streams until there is more fine grained RenderView access. Thanks to suky for providing a demo and cfg with the problem.
</change>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_streams models or other content flashing black due to color modulation render state (happened on de_cache a lot for example). Thanks to FGW for providing a demo with the problem.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.3.2</version>
<time>2015-09-11T15:03Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_input camera reacting even when input focus was lost (i.e. due to ALT+TAB).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.3.1</version>
<time>2015-09-06T13:54Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed game visuals becoming inresponsive after graphic device was lost (i.e. due to alt-tabbing out of fullscreen) after mirv_campath draw had been enabled earlier.
</change>
</changes>
</release>



<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.3.0</version>
<time>2015-08-29T10:32Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed bug in conversion between quaternion and quake engine view angles that could cause wrong campath camera view angles
epsecially when the camera was rolled.
</change>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_campath edit rotate to update the view angles also, otherwise it's not useful.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.2.6</version>
<time>2015-08-19T19:00Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_cvar_hack (for CS:GO only) - allows forcing values for some cvars (not cmds) directly, use with caution!
Please note: currently there will be neither an error (if you do a typo) nor an success message.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.2.5</version>
<time>2015-08-17T15:40Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed / improved accuracy of demo tick display in mirv_campath print.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.2.4</version>
<time>2015-08-17T13:08Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed help text of mirv_campath edit for mirv_campath edit position not being accurate.
</change>
</changes>
</release>



<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.2.3</version>
<time>2015-08-17T12:46Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed small memory / object leak in mirv_campath edit functions when a proper subset of points was selected.
</change>
<change type="updated">
Updated mirv_campath edit position: If multiple keyframes are selected the movement now applies to the middle of their bounding box (which hopefully is more useful for users).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.2.2</version>
<time>2015-08-15T13:49Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_campath edit options for editing position, rotation and FOV of selected keyframes or even rotating all or selected keyframes.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.2.1</version>
<time>2015-08-15T08:56Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated and clarified time codes for mirv_campath print and mirv_campath select.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.2.0</version>
<time>2015-08-14T17:28Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added displaying of approximate demo tick for each keyframe to mirv_campath print.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.1.0</version>
<time>2015-08-13T15:17Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_campath draw support for CS:S (Counter-Strike Source) and similar Source SDK 2013 based games.
Please let us know if it works in your mod too :-)
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
We noticed during mirv_campath draw development, that data exported by mirv_camexport might be off (not accurate enough).
If you used the data in a 3D program and can check whether or not there is a problem when syncing it to game footage,
please let us know!
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.0.3</version>
<time>2015-08-13T06:34Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed LU decomposition finally, might affect very rare cases of mirv_campath draw drawing.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.0.2</version>
<time>2015-08-12T10:20Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Bug in LU-decomposition pivotisation fixed causing bugs in line clipping.
Other minor fixes.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.0.1</version>
<time>2015-08-11T17:31Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Bug fixes mostly related to drawing.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.2.0.0</version>
<time>2015-08-11T15:12Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_campath draw. This _might_ work in other modifications than CS:GO too.
</change>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_campath select.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.1.0.0</version>
<time>2015-07-27T09:07Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_streams officially (renamed from __mirv_streams). The system still has it's limitations, but is now in a state where it makes sense
to offer it to more users. A few examples for this command will be added to the HLAE Manual hopefully.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.13.7</version>
<time>2015-07-24T17:30Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed crashes due to class pointer not being offset according to used interface in case of multiple inheritance in CAfxMesh (IMesh wrapper).
Thanks to the great and mighty anthony for providing a demo with the problem.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.13.6</version>
<time>2015-07-17T18:00Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated mirv_fov, when enabled it now has a higher priority and is only superseded by mirv_input camera and otherwise supersedes any other FOV setting (i.e. by the game or mirv_campath).
</change>
<change type="updated">
Updated and fixed __mirv_streams a bit. Depth streams are still heavily bugged though, especially when using Effect Detail higher than Low.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.13.5</version>
<time>2015-07-16T17:33Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated __mirv_streams.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.13.4</version>
<time>2015-07-14T12:02Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated __mirv_streams: Better default behaviour for matteStreams now. Also exposed lots of matteStream settings to the console
(use __mirv_streams edit),
i.e. worldTexturesAction, skyBoxTexturesAction, staticPropTexturesAction, cableAction, playerModelsAction, weaponModelsAction, shellModelsAction,
otherModelsAction, decalTexturesAction, effectsAction, shellParticleAction, otherParticleAction, stickerAction.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.13.3</version>
<time>2015-07-13T18:17Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_input camera sometimes reacting to mouse movements when console is open.
</change>
<change type="updated">
Increased default mirv_input cfg msens to 0.1.
</change>
<change type="updated">
Updated __mirv_streams: No need to copy (2) assets anymore, HLAE will mount them in the game file system instead.
For more info about testing the matte system in a early stage refer to: http://advancedfx.style-productions.net/forum/viewtopic.php?f=17&amp;t=1693
Please be aware that __mirv_streams is for testing only and subject to change.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.13.1</version>
<time>2015-07-01T17:13Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted AfxHookSource to 30th June 2015 CS:GO update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.13.0</version>
<time>2015-06-15T19:14Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_gameoverlay command for lazy people (you know who you are) that allows to disable / enable the gameoverlay.
This command is useful in AfxHookSource, since the gameoverlay will be recorded with startmovie otherwise.
Please note that this will not disable Steam notification sounds, but those are not recorded by startmovie anyway.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.12.1</version>
<time>2015-06-09T11:59Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_input camera mouse being trapped in window for POV demos.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.12.0</version>
<time>2015-06-09T07:45Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_input for input control (i.e. of camera), the command will be documented in the HLAE Manual.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.11.3</version>
<time>2015-05-27T14:05Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted AfxHookSource to 26th May 2015 CS:GO update.
</change>
<change type="updated">
Limited usable fov (Field Of View) range (affects mirv_fov and mirv_campath) to between 1 degree to 179 degrees.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.11.2</version>
<time>2015-05-08T20:10Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Turns out Visual Studio 2010 SP1 was not properly installed on the build computer, reinstalled it and updated or
rebuild all files included in the HLAE download accordingly.
Hopefully this fixes some problems on Windows 8 some users
are experiencing i.e. with AfxHookSource (but maybe not).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.11.1</version>
<time>2015-04-07T17:53Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_fov, allows to override the games FOV (Field Of View).
The features related to mirv_campath will now pick up and interpolate the FOV.
Please note that for technical reasons mirv_camexport and mirv_camimport will ignore the FOV.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
Thanks to xyanide for suggesting this feature.
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.10.2</version>
<time>2015-03-30T15:29Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed mirv_deathmsg block not ORing the blocks in the list (the last one always determined the outcome).
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
Thanks to tweeday for finding this bug.
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.10.1</version>
<time>2015-01-25T19:54Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed unitialized C++ class members leading to a crash when using mirv_campath edit functions.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
Thanks to xyanide for testing.
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.9.0</version>
<time>2015-01-22T08:50Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_snd_timescale. Allows to set the timescale for the sound system independently of host_timescale. Useful for GOTV demos with startmovie and high host_framerate where host_timescale 0 is required in order to avoid lag / skipping in recoding (set mirv_snd_timescale to 1.0).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.7.2</version>
<time>2014-11-13T20:47Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Fixed random crashes i.e. when loading a differet demo.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
Thanks to flippoz for helping.
</comments>
</release>

<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.7.1</version>
<time>2014-11-13T13:37Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Fixed mirv_cvar_unhide_all crashing.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.7.0</version>
<time>2014-11-12T17:28Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_cvar_unhide_all for CS:GO, which when executed unhides all cvars (inlcuding development cvars).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.6.0</version>
<time>2014-11-07T19:32Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_campath for creating campaths easily.
If there is a bug, then please save the campath using mirv_campath save test.xml (will go to the folder of the game.exe file) and report with that file.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
Thanks to James McEnnan for sharing qspline under the CC0 license and helping with problems!
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.5.1</version>
<time>2014-10-28T21:10Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Made AfxHookSource / mirv_deathmsg more stable against minor CS:GO client.dll updates.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.5.0</version>
<time>2014-10-22T12:06Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_deathmsg for CS:GO. Please note this will break with the next CS:GO update and either needs to be updated or hardened againt further updates then.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.4.5</version>
<time>2014-04-30T19:21Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated AfxHookSource to support 23 Apr 2014 CS:GO update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.4.4</version>
<time>2014-04-11T18:21Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated AfxHookSource to support 26 Mar 2014 CS:GO update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.4.3</version>
<time>2014-02-08T12:20Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated AfxHookSource to support 05 Feb 2014 CS:GO update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.4.2</version>
<time>2014-01-03T11:37Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated AfxHookSource to support CS:GO again.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.4.1</version>
<time>2013-06-12T17:40Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Fixed CS:GO crashing in some situations.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to how-hiGh!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.4.0</version>
<time>2013-06-11T19:15Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Updated AfxHookSource to support more modifications for Camera Motion Data I/O.
Also made AfxHookSource more stable against game updates.
The exact Source engine modifications supported are unknown at the moment and need to be tested.
Currently known to work: Counter-Strike:Source, Counter-Strike:Global Offensive.
Please note: Currently CS:GO will crash when the demo end is reached, we couldn't fix this so far.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to Dec and how-hiGh!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.34</version>
<time>2013-05-26T14:34Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 20 May 2013 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to how-hiGh!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.33</version>
<time>2013-05-14T17:23Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 29 Apr 2013 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to xQd!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.32</version>
<time>2013-03-23T19:48Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 20 Mar 2013 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to how-hiGh!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.31</version>
<time>2013-02-09T14:14Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 5 Feb 2013 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to how-hiGh!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.30</version>
<time>2012-10-13T17:48Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 24 Sep 2012 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to Dec!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.29</version>
<time>2012-09-14T18:28Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 11 Sep 2012 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to how-hiGh!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.28</version>
<time>2012-08-25T18:24Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 22 Aug 2012 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to how-hiGh!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.27</version>
<time>2012-07-04T16:43Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 03 Jul 2012 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to how-hiGh!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.26</version>
<time>2012-05-27T17:11Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 22 May 2012 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to how-hiGh!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.25</version>
<time>2012-02-12T14:51Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 09 Feb 2012 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to Dec!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.24</version>
<time>2011-12-24T16:36Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 22 Dec 2011 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to how-hiGh!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.23</version>
<time>2011-12-21T14:29Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 16 Dec 2011 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to Dec!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.22</version>
<time>2011-11-15T17:24Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 08 Nov 2011 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to Dec!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.21</version>
<time>2011-10-30T17:59Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 26 Oct 2011 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to Dec!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.20</version>
<time>2011-09-29T13:38Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 17 Sep 2011 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.19</version>
<time>2011-08-26T13:31Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 04 Aug 2011 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.18</version>
<time>2011-07-08T17:31Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 08 July 2011 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to Dec!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.17</version>
<time>2011-06-28T19:02Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 28 June 2011 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks and greetings to Dec!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.16</version>
<time>2011-05-10T21:46Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 10 May 2011 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.15</version>
<time>2011-04-24T18:50Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 21 Apr 2011 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks to ne0n for helping!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.14</version>
<time>2011-04-18T18:44Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 15 Apr 2011 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks again to Shift for helping!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.13</version>
<time>2011-03-05T18:20Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 04 Mar 2011 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>Thanks to Shift for helping!</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.12</version>
<time>2010-12-22T18:44Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 22 Dec 2010 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.11</version>
<time>2010-12-20T20:21Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 18 Dec 2010 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.10</version>
<time>2010-10-31T17:50Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 30 Oct 2010 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>



<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.9</version>
<time>2010-10-07T17:30Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 07 Oct 2010 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.8</version>
<time>2010-09-10T09:56Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 09 Sep 2010 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.7</version>
<time>2010-09-01T15:49Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 01 Sep 2010 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.6</version>
<time>2010-08-31T12:37Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 30 Aug 2010 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
Playing demos and using the hook with those should work.
Joing servers might crash the game or get you banned.
Please launch CSS at least once without HLAE.
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.5</version>
<time>2010-06-28T08:50Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 26 Jun 2010 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.4</version>
<time>2010-06-24T22:23Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Adjusted to 23 Jun 2010 CSS update.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.3</version>
<time>2010-06-01T22:53Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="fixed">
Fixed cam motion file import.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
Thanks to chetaah.
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.2</version>
<time>2010-05-20T17:32Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="removed">
Removed mirv_allowcheats (sv_cheats always works in demos in Source).
</change>
<change type="updated">
Switched to VC100.
</change>
</changes>
</release>

<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.3.1</version>
<time>2010-04-04T19:11Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_allowcheats (cstrike, ep2), unblocks sv_cheats and related commands.
</change>
<change type="added">
Extended mirv_camexport, mirv_camimport to work with ep2.
</change>
</changes>
<comments>
Greetz / thx to msthavoc, Austin Killey, nemoic.
</comments>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.2.1</version>
<time>2009-12-22T10:13Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="updated">
Minor tweak in camimport to reduce rounding error.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.2.0</version>
<time>2009-11-02T14:00Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
Added mirv_camexport, mirv_camimport (Counter-Strike Source only).
</change>
</changes>
</release>


<release>
<name>AfxHookSource</name>
<version>0.0.0.1</version>
<time>2009-09-29T22:00Z</time>
<changes>
<change type="added">
First version.
</change>
</changes>
</release>


</changelog>